(SOUNDS SOUND)
(KLIMPERN)
(FAUCHEN)
(CLICK-KLACK, PING)
(PIANO TONES)
(GEESE SNAKES)
(HECHELT)
(KICHERN)
huh?
I have you!
(WAU)
Ha-ha!
And caught again!
Oh, come on, Knickohr, don't look at me like that!
Well, it's your turn!
(WAU)
(TRAMPELN)
(MUHEN)
KUEHNER BLICK: The bison give us a sign.
You know, the cold season is approaching.
We must warn others.
humph.
huh?
oh! (LAUGHS)
Now you have me!
(WIEHERN)
Ooh!
(SNORT)
(WIEHERT)
YAKARI: Oh!
It looks like...
(SNORT)
That's Little Thunder!
oh!
Did you see that?
That was Little Thunder. The fastest pony in the prairie.
All Sioux know him!
I wish I could get closer to him.
RAINBOW: Yakari!
Want archery with us? - Not now.
Yakari always has something better in front of him.
I go to the village, I find someone.
You're just afraid of losing to a girl.
what?
Ha! You have no chance, rainbow.
Fair enough. Can I practice at least a little bit.
Yakari! - Father!
Come back and help your mother!
Do you think one day I can ride on Little Thunder?
On Little Thunder? No, certainly not.
Our best hunters have tried, no one has succeeded.
caution!
Excuse me!
forgiveness!
I'm sorry.
oh! - Hey!
(GÄHNT)
Just leave, I'll do it.
Excuse me, tired warriors!
Thank you, my son.
Hey, everyone's in such a weird hurry today.
Yes, later is a meeting at the big oak.
The elders will tell us some important things.
Take a break, you will need your strength...
(LAUGHS)
(YAKARI LAUGHS)
(KNICKOHR BELLT)
Wait here for me, kink ear.
aha!
They collect all the supplies!
I greet you!
(YAKARI LAUGHS)
Hello, flying squirrels.
Don't worry, I haven't forgotten you.
(VÖGEL ZWITSCHERN)
oh!
The Bärentatzen Mountains.
(WIEHERN)
Juhuuh!
oh!
Juhuh!
(ADLER KREISCHT)
(CIRCLE)
Juhuh!
Aah!
Yakari! What are you doing?
(LAUGHS)
I had a great dream!
I could fly!
Like an eagle!
And I was a huge eagle myself!
You know, dreams tell a lot about who dreams them.
Yes, and whoever sees the eagle in a dream,
expects an extraordinary fate.
An extraordinary fate?
RAINBOW: Yakari!
And, what was it like?
It was such a stupid wind...
(KCHERT)
This morning I saw Little Thunder.
real? Little thunder?
(FRÖSCHE QUAKEN)
(BRUMMT MELODIE)
Excuse me, tired warriors!
Sit down and be still, children.
Still rock speaks to us.
Psst, is he really as fast as everyone says?
Uh, who? Tired warrior?
nonsense! Little thunder! Who else?! - Rest! Be quiet!
Be quiet! - Children, have respect!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Sh!
(KCHERT)
In their unfathomable wisdom, the bison have recognized that
that they must leave their pastures,
and thus show us the way.
You all know that our tribe cannot live without the bison.
That is why the time has come.
We must now leave and follow in their footsteps.
We have to move away from here.
The time of the Great Winds is coming soon.
These raging hurricanes destroy everything,
what is in their way!
oh! - Ah!
They are faster than a galloping Mustang.
No man or animal can survive the great winds.
(SNORING)
(RÄUSPERN)
Thank you, the-all-white.
Bold look, is everything prepared?
Yes, but we still lack some Mustangs
for the long, arduous journey.
At sunrise we look!
(MURMELN DURCHEINANDER)
Hey! Do we want to follow the hunters tomorrow?
no! My father doesn't allow that. - Schh!
Only the brave are allowed to catch a wild Mustang.
I am brave!
But brave people wear the bravery feather!
Hey, wait!
Little thunder might be among the Mustangs.
WTF?
Where are they all so quickly?
Uaah!
(LACHEN)
Wait for me!
We would have to see them right away!
Are you sure? - Yes.
JÄGER: Forward!
Drive them together!
(WIEHERN)
Little thunder!
Yes, he is! - Have I told you!
Beware, they'll see us yet!
(WIEHERT)
no!
wow!
We never catch this pony.
(WIEHERT)
Little thunder!
Let's go before the hunters see us.
Go back without me.
what? - No, Yakari!
nevertheless. The tribe soon moves away and then I don't get to him anymore.
Don't worry, I'm back quickly.
No, kink ear, that's not possible. Little Thunder is terrified.
Come on, be good!
(JAULT)
This time he gets really upset.
Yes, his parents will not be pleased.
Knickohr, follow him!
(SCHLUCKT)
(WIEHERN)
(WIEHERT)
oh!
what...? oh!
You're stuck!
Don't worry, Little Thunder.
(WIEHERT)
Nothing is broken. Well, I'm very careful.
Everything is fine again.
(WIEHERT)
Calm down. Don't be afraid.
Very slowly...
Calm down.
Hey, not so wild! I've got it right away!
(BRUMMELT)
Are we both friends now?
Hey! (BELLEN)
(LAUGHS)
Little Thunder was just here!
And I helped him!
oh!
I so much hope to see him again.
(ADLER KREISCHT)
wow!
oh!
wow! You look like the eagle in my dream!
I'm a big eagle.
Your totem, your protector.
Wherever you go, I go too.
wow!
It was very generous that you saved Little Thunder.
Do you think we both will become friends at some point?
and riding through the prairie?
For your courage and kindness
I give you my most beautiful feather.
wow!
Thank you, Big Eagle.
Such feathers are worn by the brave of the tribe!
Does that mean I'm one of the brave ones now?
Everyone who knows how to live in peace with all living beings
and respect for them is courageous.
But I want to give you something else.
Something that no one has ever owned before.
You give me something else?
Go with it!
What kind of gift?
Aaaaaah!
wow!
But that was not a dream!
(SINGS) Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, ho, ha, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, ho, ha, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, ha, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, ho, ha, hey...
(BELLT)
Look, knickers!
Just such a feather are worn by all the brave!
Yes, great, Yakari, but let's go home now.
what? Aah!
Yakari!
Hey, I understood what you just said.
And every word!
You are right! And so do I!
Then you understand me: let's go back!
Then is the gift of The Great Eagle,
that I have the gift of talking to animals?
(LAUGHS)
Do you know what that means?
Uh, yes. We go back to the tribe?
no! (LAUGHS)
That means I can talk to Little Thunder!
Hey! This is not the way to the village!
The trail of Little Thunder ends here on this stone path.
He certainly ran into the forest.
You don't want to go in there! There are wild beasts in the forest!
I have to talk to him!
You can be dogish, but maybe not a horse!
YAKARI: There are no traces here.
I can ask the other forest dwellers.
Then we see if other animals understand me.
Other animals? Do you mean the beasts?
Yakari?
Hello? Yakari?
shh!
Never do anything like this to me again! - Schh!
huh?
Beep, beep, do you see the little man?
What does he do alone in the forest?
And this dog doesn't look like he can protect him!
Hey birds! I can understand you.
what?
Did you happen to see a pony that...?
Hey, hey, that starts really well.
(DEER GRUNZT)
(SCHNARCHT)
oh! Hello, Owl!
ah!
I'm sorry.
So you understand me.
Did a pony come by here?
You can't just sneak in and get rid of it!
Bla, blah, blah!
moment! You speak my language!
Mhm.
I am Yakari.
And I am speechless!
How rude to scare me so much!
Oh yes, your pony is long!
oh. Thank you, Owl! And apologize.
Oah!
Hey, little butterfly, you understand me too, don't you?
yes.
Have you seen a pony here?
(ALL SCHMETTERLINGE REDEN MESSE)
So I don't understand a word!
Now I understand. That's where he ran!
Thank you, butterflies!
You're welcome...
Please don't say you want to talk to the ants.
(LAUGHS) Well come!
My father showed me how to read tracks.
This is of Little Thunder.
Now it's enough with this pony! We have to go home!
But I don't want to. Thanks to Großer Adler's gift, I can now talk to him!
Surely we will be friends!
You already have a friend!
I know that, Knickohr. Let's go, come on!
(GEESE SNAKES)
Oah!
Wait here for me.
If it has to be.
When the wild beasts leave me alone.
(SNORT)
(WIEHERT)
Um... - (WIEHERT)
Don't be afraid.
Um, my name is Yakari.
(WIEHERT)
I can understand you.
yes! A gift from Big Eagle, my totem.
Now I can talk to all the animals!
I think Little Thunder...
What is "Little Thunder"?
That's you!
The name was given to you by my tribe, the Sioux:
Little thunder, the pony that's as fast as the lightning!
What are they doing?
Um, what does your hoof do? Does he still hurt?
No, it's going to happen again.
But thank you for helping me.
(WIEHERT)
Hey! What should it be?
Me, uh... I thought we are friends and...
You can talk to the animals, can you?
Next time you ask first!
Little thunder! Wait!
Please stay here!
You have a gift, Yakari,
but otherwise you are like all people.
You just think of yourself!
Oh no.
Wait!
Little thunder!
(WIEHERT)
YAKARI: No!
Little thunder!
(BELLT)
oh! ah!
Aah!
Oh no! Yakari!
Yakari!
(BELLT)
Aah!
oh!
Knickohr, no!
Aah!
(KNICKOHR BELLT)
Aaah!
(JAULT)
(WIEHERT)
Oh no!
lot! Get the people!
(WIEHERT)
(WIEHERN)
Hoo! Calm down. gently. quiet.
Don't worry! Beautifully quiet! So is good!
We told him not to go! - But he didn't want to hear!
Yakari has never gone that far.
And never alone.
I sent Knickohr, but it's gone.
All my fault. I wanted to follow the hunters.
No, children, that's not your fault.
We are looking for our son, shimmering braids.
But first I have to talk to the elders.
Thank you both for your help.
Sh!
uh...?
(STÖHNT)
oh...
(HEARTBEAT)
What do you want, rainbow? - Schh!
Kühner Blick says he is looking for his son.
The elders say they understand this,
but the tribe cannot wait for them.
real? We can't leave without Yakari!
The trunk must break up quickly.
Soon the Great Winds will move through this area.
Little badger and I want to help find Yakari.
yes! uh... what?
No, you stay here, the tribe needs help moving.
The search for Yakari could become dangerous.
yes! He is absolutely right.
Let's go now! To work!
linden tree! Where are you?
(SCHNARCHT)
Hey!
I think I'm dreaming! It's fantastic, rodent!
And what do you call it? "Cutting teeth with beaver"?
All immediately to the dam! Make it!
oh! What a disaster!
This will take a long time for our dam to work again!
Don't you see?
To work! lot!
Hey, hey, hey. All right.
Quite quietly, a thousand mouths.
First of all, we take care of it.
here.
Let us be careful. That's a little human being!
I didn't know they were growing on trees.
Hello, beaver.
Could you pull me out?
I think I'm standing in the woods! He speaks Beaver!
Hello! I am linden tree.
I am Yakari. - Oh!
(BELLT)
Go, kink ear, look Yakari!
YAKARI: All I know is how I cling to the tree,
and then crash down the waterfall.
No idea how long I've been driving along the river.
Then you saved me.
(SEUFZEN)
humph.
Do you see these rocks? These are the Bärentatzen Mountains.
From the tree they looked much bigger.
(SEUFZEN)
My parents are so far away from here.
How sad!
People also have parents?
Oh no! Where is my pen?
Ooh...
My parents and friends are certainly very worried.
(SEUFZEN)
And my father was right.
No one can catch Little Thunder.
I just wanted us to be friends.
friends? You have a friend. myself!
(LAUGHS)
Thank you, Lindenbaum, but...
I have to go home now.
Thank you, beaver. - Do it well. reunion!
hooray! Jippie!
LINDENBAUM: Are we there soon?
You have to go home now.
Oh, Yakari.
Oh, what's the point? See you again!
linden tree! Back to work!
I'm already running!
Lindenbaum, what is to be that?
If I run like this, I will come to the dam later and the others are ready.
From a distance, it looks like...
I see that very carefully!
See you!
(BREATHES HARD)
(ADLER KREISCHT)
oh!
Big eagle!
Do not lose the courage, Yakari,
for I will never leave you.
I don't deserve your trust.
I lost my pen.
And my courage.
Well, there is still a long way to go.
A hard road.
You must face the giant and mother of earth's wrath.
In these trials, your courage is shown.
Trust in you, Yakari!
Big eagle!
Which giants? Mother Earth's wrath?
What does Big Eagle mean? huh?
My tribe!
Father! Mother! I am here!
huh?
Oh no!
Aah!
(WIEHERN)
ah!
Aah!
Yakari! Are you okay?
Little thunder!
Jump on my back!
I ride on Little Thunder! Jippieh!
Be quiet! You put us all in danger!
The hunters are behind us!
yes! - Let's go!
You saved me!
You are far away from home, so alone. - I...
You should not have left your tribe!
actually...
You are far too young. - But...
You worry about me!
That's why you came back!
Uh, yes.
Go back to your people. Let these dangerous stupidities!
So you don't bring me back to the tribe
and will not be my friend?
(SEUFZT)
No, Yakari, I cannot be free among you human beings.
Ooh...
yes! - Hoo!
(LAUGHTER AND CHEERS)
Hey!
Leave the nonsense, you're going to drive the Mustangs crazy!
Aah!
We cannot allow this to happen!
Oh, really? This morning Sioux hunters have caught horses!
Yes, but they would never hurt them!
(SEUFZT)
(WIEHERN)
Don't act like that!
Stupid cattle!
These people! - We are not watching!
You are faster than the horses of the Pumafell hunters.
You lure them into the valley and I free the Mustangs!
okay. But be careful!
I'm not close this time when something goes wrong.
Of course, I am cautious.
I know what I'm doing!
I have played very often with kink-ear hiding places.
what?
(WIEHERN)
(WIEHERT)
ah!
Ha, ha, ha!
That's mine! You're waxing the Mustangs!
Uh, me?
Do you think you're going to get that?
(WIEHERN)
impudence.
I have to sit around here and they have all the fun...
huh?
JÄGER: Let's go, faster!
(HUNTER LAUGHS)
Shame! Don't be afraid.
Ha, ha, ha, the horse is pretty much scouring you around, what?
humph...
Sh! Now disappear here. quiet!
Ha, ha, ha!
This also applies to you if you want.
I am not used to a person being kind to me.
I never forget that, little man.
Ha, ha, ha!
(JÄGER CALL)
afterwards! - Faster!
Haah!
(WIEHERT)
What a precious and noble horse!
Ha, ha, ha, what great hunters you are!
But not big enough to catch a tiny horse!
What are you doing up there? You should keep watch!
You idiot!
Someone crawled here for a long time.
The track leads to the rocks there.
There is no point!
Did you get rid of our horses, you dwarf mosquito?
All alone?
You are a Sioux!
You have nothing to look for in our hunting grounds!
Fast, Yakari, jump up!
Yes-hah!
You're against a Sioux as small as a beaver?
After him!
no! Not now!
We are only threatened with shame by this horse.
(WOLF HOWLING)
(LAUGHS) They don't get behind us!
The horses are all free!
(SINGS) Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, ho, ha, hey...
That's right, and you were very brave, Yakari,
but unfortunately we are stuck here.
humph...
We take the way over the mountains.
The hunting grounds of the Sioux are on the other side.
no.
The mountains are so high. It's going to be difficult!
That would be a long road for both of us.
And terribly cold!
Do you really trust yourself to cross this mountain?
um...
humph...
Well, Big Eagle said,
when I set myself the giant and mother of earth wrath,
will show my courage.
Yes, with the giants he certainly meant the mountains!
Now I understand that's the way home!
You're a real big head.
Don't you want to come along, Little Thunder?
Um, well... I can't leave you alone.
It's the only way we face the giants!
yes! We face the giants!
Because of you, we didn't catch a Mustang today!
(SCHLUCKT)
And his own horse is gone, too.
I know these mountains here.
I'm going to catch this horse!
humph...
(LACHEN)
If not, I will never return to our tribe!
Howgh!
(LAUGHS)
Well, then it says, live well!
Go!
(HUNTER LAUGHS)
Ooh!
The child and this horse have no chance in this mountain world.
When they come back exhausted,
we will expect them.
(BELLEN)
(BELLT)
Yakari follows a horse.
Our son is unreasonable.
He will never ride on Little Thunder.
Yakari's tracks lead to the river.
There are no footprints on the side, only hoof marks!
(KNICKOHR BELLT)
(BELLT)
Yesterday Yakari appeared in a dream a big eagle.
This feather is a sign. Our son is still alive, Bold look!
But very soon the Great Winds are coming over us.
This valley is...
... the home of the Pumafelle, our enemies.
Let us look for our son!
(GESANG) High up, high.
high.
High up, over mountain and valley.
High up where the bird flies.
So high.
Two friends, oho-ho-ho,
no matter what happens.
Companions for all eternity.
(KNURREN)
Oh, here apparently a bear has its territory.
Be careful, Yakari!
(KNURRT)
Hey, hello, you little bear!
Maybe I don't speak bearish?
Oh no, what's going on, little bear?
Um, weren't you afraid when I just roared like that?
Are you kidding? I've never been so scared!
Or, Little Thunder? - Come on, we have to go!
(KNURRT)
Come on, get away here. - It's small.
Go! Where there is a bear cub, there must also be a bear mother.
(KNURRT)
Great, I'm very proud of you, honeydew!
You become a big bear!
To scare a little person so much, wonderful!
(SUMMT MELODIE)
(LAUGHS)
(WOLF HOWLING)
(YAKARI GÄHNT)
(MAGEN KNURRT)
ah!
(LACHEN)
Hello, bird!
(LAUGHS GRIMLY)
Ha! This is far too easy!
(SMALL BEAR KNURRT)
(KNURRT)
Aah!
(SCREAMS)
(SCHREIT)
I really scared him!
Oh yes, great, honeydew!
(VÖGEL KRÄHEN)
YAKARI: Hey!
Yakari!
Are you hurt?
"Are you hurt," you poor little ones?
(LACHEN)
Nothing happens. I only picked berries with my friend.
And then three naughty ravens attacked me.
yes! But Yakari expelled them.
Yakari! You always disappear and there is trouble!
From now on you will stay near me!
Oh, you two are probably best friends?
yes. - Oh no!
Anyway.
By the way, they call me Little Wings.
Because of me, you know,
Giant wings.
(SMALL WINGS LAUGHS)
humph...
(SMALL WINGS PFEIFT MELODIE)
(SMALL WINGS CRUNCHING MELODY)
What do you have, Yakari?
The Great Winds soon reach my tribe,
and I don't come back in time.
If I had wings like A Big Eagle,
I could fly to our village.
I can fly for you.
real? Would you do that for me?
But you're so small, that's way too far for you.
You don't know what we birds can do!
I fly from where the sun rises,
to where the moon goes down.
Fly up the river, you see a brown dog with a kink ear.
Surely he is looking for me.
Tell him I'm fine, I'm going over the mountains.
You don't have to worry.
Hey, did you understand that?
clear! I fly up the river, i see a dog with a kink ear,
who is looking for you.
I say you go over the mountains, no need to worry.
(PFEIFT)
Goodbye, my friends!
Ju-huh-huh!
Hey, but not there long!
Was just fun! Ha ha!
Do it well!
See you soon, Little Wings! Thank you very much!
SMALL DONNER: Watch out for you!
(WIND PFEIFT)
(PFEIFT MELODIE)
(LACHEN)
Now the little man can no longer protect you!
I promised It to Yakari!
I get you!
How mean.
With such small wings, it flies much easier.
ouch!
(LAUGHS)
Hui!
Poor Yakari.
All alone and no great one there to protect him.
Sleep, my little darling.
I should have gone along!
Be quiet! Some beavers have to work tomorrow!
Tss!
Yakari is lucky. So alone, without adults.
(YAKARI SCHLOTTERT)
Well, Yakari, climb on my back.
You're just as tired as I am.
And I can still go.
Ooh!
(KECKERT)
ah!
(WOLF HOWLING)
(KECKERN)
At night it is even colder here.
(KECKERT)
Best of all, we hide in the cave.
Don't be afraid, weird squirrel.
Can we go in?
(KECKERN)
Oh, nice warm, the straw.
Do you think we will be there in time tomorrow?
Yes, but we have to rest first.
Ha, ha, there!
My name is Yakari, and that's Little Thunder.
I know that! I'm already following you up the whole mountain!
I'm ringtail.
I've never seen an animal like you.
How should you? I am not coming from here.
But it was too hot at home.
I need it cooler and wanted to see something different.
Schh.
I've never seen snow!
Where can I find it?
You can't find snow, ringtail.
The snow finds you.
Yes, really? - Schh!
quiet!
Excuse me.
Forget: I'm nocturnal, see you tomorrow!
(THUNDER)
(SCHNARCHT)
Schh! Quickly gone!
ouch!
Really a great idea! - Schh! Not so loud!
That's crazy! In the night into the wilderness!
We have to go to Yakari, he needs us!
No, children!
It is the tribe that needs you.
We leave at dusk.
The big winds are here tomorrow.
But Yakari is...
Don't worry! His parents are on his trail.
Did I tell you!
Hmm...
Bold look, shimmering braids,
find your son quickly and bring you to safety.
Tomorrow, mischief will come upon us.
(THUNDER)
(RINGELSCHWANZ SCHNARCHT)
Uaah!
oh!
(LAUGHS)
Thank you, ringtail! Such a delicious breakfast.
Oh, excuse me.
Goodbye, Yakari.
I want to sleep now.
SMALL DONNER: Hey Yakari! Come here!
Thank you again. See you soon, ringtail!
oh!
A great surprise awaits ringtail!
(WIEHERT)
(MOWER)
oh!
(LAUGHS)
Without you, I would never have been able to face the giant.
You were very brave, Yakari.
You can be on my back whenever you want.
If you think about it... - ... to ask you beforehand?
I promise that!
Hey, do you fancy a little race?
Who is first at the pine?
Hui! Exactly!
(GRUMMELT)
Nothing like getting out! A wonderful day is waiting for me!
Juhuuh!
ah!
Hmm. Hä?
What kind of stuff is that?
Yesterday it wasn't there!
Bah!
Very disgustingly soft and cold! What is the point of this?
Of course! That's snow!
(WIEHERT)
Ha! What comes to mind? This is my horse!
Let us be at peace!
Get out there, dwarf!
You are too small for a great hunter like me!
Little Thunder is my friend! No one is going to do anything to him!
Well wait!
Aah!
Yakari!
Oh no!
I'm already doing it! Hui!
Yakari!
Yakari! Yakari!
Oh man, oh man!
Now do! Wake up!
Ha!
Yakari!
Ringtail?
But where is Little Thunder?
Little thunder is going well. He's waiting outside.
Oh, thank you very much.
Woah!
That's beautiful here!
Yes of course. Great.
But we have to get away from here! This Puma...
He's still somewhere here! - Puma?
oh! This was not a puma, this is a human being!
what? That is even worse.
Aaah!
Quickly get away here!
Yakari!
I know this cave!
You only come out here if you...
help me catch the horse!
never!
Let's go, long!
Come on! Be good, little Sioux!
Tell me where the horse is!
Then I will bring you home!
I am your friend!
You're not my friend! You'll never be!
Uaah!
Stop it!
Hey, hey!
Oh no!
You didn't expect that.
Look! Looks like a frozen river.
I bet it leads outside.
Come with you to the prairie. It's safer.
Oh no no. Just go there.
The Puma is too stupid for a clever ringtail like me.
I prefer to stay here and enjoy the snow!
but... Wait!
humph... We'll see you again.
( SCHLUCK)
Little thunder?
I'm sorry, Big Eagle.
I have to disappoint you.
But I am... too weak for the way.
Little thunder?
Is that you?
That's it, little Sioux! Enough played!
You are to blame for this horse repeatedly escaping me!
stop!
Leave my son!
Father! - Yakari!
Are you hurt? - It's enough for me with you!
Yakari!
Come, my son!
Mother!
We were so worried.
Get lost!
Go to your Pumafuren!
(BELLT)
(KNICKOHR BELLT)
Yakari, go to your people where you are at home.
Knickohr! Och!
There you are!
Thank you, you did it wonderfully!
Without your friend, the bird, we would never have found you.
Quickly, we have to go!
The storm is about to break out!
We have to go back to the tribe! come!
oh!
Little thunder.
Little thunder!
Little Thunder...
Don't you hear, Yakari?
I can't... - The tribe needs us now!
Small thunder is intmitable. He is not a friend of man.
(WIND PFEIFT)
There!
Let's follow the animals, they know where to go.
(WINSELT)
"Mother Earth's Wrath"!
Big eagle meant the hurricanes!
Our horses are completely exhausted!
We need a miracle!
oh!
Come Yakari! Jump up!
Little thunder!
good! And now away here!
This pony!
You never make it this way! We have to wait a long time here!
Yakari! What are you up to?
Father! This way!
Follow me!
Wait for us, Yakari!
no!
It's enough for me. That's it.
This is not a job for a hunter like me.
(BELLT)
You're back!
Hey!
(SCHNARCHT)
SMALL DACHS: Where is Yakari?
(WIEHERN)
There he is!
(WIEHERT)
Little thunder!
Is this your horse now?
no.
He's my friend.
Ho, ho, ho.
(LACHEN)
Yes, Yakari!
(KCHERT)
Shimmering braids and bold looks can be proud of their son.
He has asserted himself all alone in the wilderness.
And Yakari came back to us on the back of the wildest wild horse.
You deserve this eagle feather as a symbol of your great courage.
oh!
The feather that Big Eagle gave me!
Well done, my son.
We are proud of you!
That was strong!
(CHEERING AND LAUGHING)
(WIEHERT)
(GESANG) Yakari!
Yakari
and his best friend.
Children of the prairie,
what a child only dreams of.
Big Eagle
watches over him.
His friends are the animals,
the wind and the river.
Yakari
and his best friend.
Children of the prairie,
what a child only dreams of.
Yakari,
Yakari.
Subtitles by Till Rudolph textile image refrigerator.